REGETTA HARRIS

regettaspearman@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven Information Technology Professional with current CRM, database management, and website development experience (i.e., two years of experience in the field). Accounting and financial expert with recent SQL training and work experience managing a database of over 30,000 accounts. Excellent attention to detail with a proven track record for completing multiple projects simultaneously within deadlines. Additional skills include the following:

OneCause

eTapestry

WealthEngine

Ellucian Banner

Double the Donation

- Salesforce CRM
- Salesforce Marketing Cloud
- SQL (Intermediate) Ruffalo Noel Levitz CampusCall

EDUCATION

Guilford Technical Community College	Greensboro, NC
Certificate in Information Technology – Database Management	May 2022
University of North Carolina - Greensboro	Greensboro, NC

University of North Carolina - Greensboro Master of Science - Accounting

June 2018

Northcentral University Prescott, AZ **Post Baccalaureate Certificate in Training and Development** July 2015

East Carolina University Greenville, NC

Master of Business Administration Dec. 2013

University of North Carolina - Greensboro Greensboro, NC

Bachelor of Science - Accounting May 2010

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cone Health - Philanthropy

Greensboro, NC

Prospect Research and Database Coordinator

Feb. 2020 - Current

Create profiles, perform research, and locate prospective donors using analytics and wealth screening data. Charged with updating and maintaining a database of 30,000 prospects and donors. Additional duties include segmenting patient population for solicitation, building fundraising website, and on demand report building for all team members. Achievements include:

- Successful database migration in June 2021 from eTapestry to Salesforce
- Creation of donor pipeline monitoring process in January 2022
- Active Member, ConeX Team (i.e., patient experience team responsible for reviewing newly introduced projects for the entire system in terms of how it would impact the patient)

North Carolina A&T State University – Office of Annual Giving

Greensboro, NC

Call Center Manager

Nov. 2016 - Jan. 2020

Recruited, interviewed, hired, trained, and managed a team of 20 student fundraisers. Prepared nightly, weekly, and monthly reports while actively managing the incentive program. Handled escalations and resolved issues regarding the Call Center. Achievements included:

Monitored and coached student callers on techniques to improve fundraising and customer service skills

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Bank of America Greensboro, NC

Multiple Positions June 2010 – Dec. 2016

Customer Relationship Manager

July 2014 - Dec. 2016

Nov. 2007 - Current

Served as a liaison between the short sale and foreclosure departments charged with resolving account delinquency (e.g., employee accounts, government loans, home equity loans, and lines of credit). Performed account research to find payment errors and made corrections accordingly. Floor walker and subject matter expert for the team and served as the only point of contact for a portfolio of approximately 100 customers in various stages of delinquency/home retention. Achievements included:

- Promoted to Officer in August 2012
- Top Performer each quarter in Q3-2014 to Q2-2016

Customer Advocate June 2013 – July 2014

Respond to written correspondence (i.e., complaints and general inquiries) received from a variety of Regulators, Government/Business Agencies (OCC, CFPB, BBB, State Attorney General Offices), and directly from consumers. Managed risk to the company by handling inquiries in accordance with department and regulatory guidelines. Set expectations with consumers on timeliness of responses as well as accuracy of data provided during research using backup documentation. Accomplishments included:

- Top Quality Performer for 2013 (Customer Advocate)
- Top Performer in December 2013, January 2014, February 2014, April 2014 (Customer Advocate)

Proficiency Coach October 2011 – June 2013

Coached a team of 40 CRMs on their day-to-day role, quality, and workflow management in the multi-lien and 2nd lien segment (all investors and lien positions). Served as the liaison between quality team and CRMs. Led trainings as indicated by business needs, which included delivering weekly huddles to support teams (mini trainings) and performing call listening sessions and side-by-sides for all associates supported. Accomplishments included:

- Served as the only subject matter expert in the multi-lien and 2nd lien segments
- Developed and implemented 2nd Lien Road Show Trained associates at five (5) different sites along the East Coast on 2nd Lien Product

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Zeta Phi Beta Sorority, Inc. – The Beta Nu Zeta Chapter: Greensboro, NC

Brito Food Market: Greensboro, NC
 Nov. 2021 – Current